<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://lunardustx.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://lunardustx.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Final Project</title>
      <link>https://lunardustx.github.io/embodied-interaction/final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lunardustx.github.io/embodied-interaction/final-project/</guid>
      <description>Final Showcase Project Description The idea of this project is to explore the forest in your own room with the help of HoloLens. You could catch fireflies and interact with mushrooms in this project.
Development Process Firefly Catch This was the first thing I made for this project, because firefly is a very typical forest element.
At the beginning, I planned to use a real bug net to catch fireflies. But I quickly dropped this idea after a simple mock test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Project Proposal</title>
      <link>https://lunardustx.github.io/embodied-interaction/final-project-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lunardustx.github.io/embodied-interaction/final-project-proposal/</guid>
      <description>AR technology is a bridge between virtual and reality. With the help of AR glasses, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to see something fantasy.
The basic idea of this project is super simple: use a tangible object as a trigger, to make something happen in the virtual world.
Araddin Lamp The first idea came into my mind is Araddin Magic Lamp, the famous folk tale in the book One Thousand and One Nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gesture Assignment</title>
      <link>https://lunardustx.github.io/embodied-interaction/gesture-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lunardustx.github.io/embodied-interaction/gesture-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Core Gesture At first, we found the &amp;ldquo;opening pinched fingers&amp;rdquo; gesture looks like the process of bloom, it would be natural to use this gesture to plant a flower. We decided to create a gardening experience based on this gesture.
Interface Then, we designed a simple interface for users to select, scale, and create flowers. The &amp;ldquo;select&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;scale&amp;rdquo; gestures are two common gestures in widely used in other projects. We chose them as complementary gestures to enhance the gardening experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Braintrainer</title>
      <link>https://lunardustx.github.io/projects/math-brain-trainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lunardustx.github.io/projects/math-brain-trainer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise Surprise</title>
      <link>https://lunardustx.github.io/articles/article/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lunardustx.github.io/articles/article/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your support! Hello. If you like this template, I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to get a coffee donation :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
